Sign up

Log in

SubscribeStar.com Privacy Policy
================================

Updated: November 09, 2024 03:16 am

* * *

### General statement

We do not disclose, share, or sell Users’ Personal Information we collected to any third parties for any monetary or commercial benefit.  
  
The terms "you", “yours”, "your" refer to any User - Subscriber, Star, Referral Associate, or visitor - that uses this Website (aka “Platform” or “Service”) in accordance with our Terms of Service.

* * *

### Collected information

We collect information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular User, or device (“Personal Information”). In particular, Service collects and has collected from its consumers within the last twelve (12) months the following categories of Personal Information:  

* Personal identifiers - a set of information you provide for subscriptions or during the sign-up process via our Website, including your first and last name, alias (i.e, Nickname), email address, or any personal identifiers you submit to us when communicating with us.
* Transaction information you provide when you make a subscription on this Website, such as your first and last name, and Payment data or Financial Information.
* Financial Information (i.e., Payment data) is the information you provide when you make a subscription or request a payout through our Website, such as your bank account number, and other related data.
* Internet connectivity, usage, and activity information about your use, and the use by any person(s) you authorize or supervise, of our Website, including the content you view, browser device and type, unique device identifier and/or Internet Protocol (IP) address, and information about your interactions with our Website.
* Location information, including geolocation information provided through our Website’s server logs or associated with your Internet Protocol (IP) address, where we are permitted by law to process this information.

* * *

### Payment data

Payment data must be collected before processing subscriptions, refunds, or payouts.  
  
As a Subscriber, you must provide your payment data to our payment processors and other partnering financial institutions. During this process, this Platform does not receive your full card number. Payment processors provide this Platform with a secure token that represents the corresponding User account, payment method’s expiration date, card type, and the last four digits of the card number only. If Users are required to provide their full name to the payment processor, then they also provide us with that information.  
  
To receive payouts via means other than a bank account, our Users (i.e. Stars) have to create an account with one of our payment partners. We will also require bank account information to process payouts for those who chose to proceed with the bank transfer. Users must also provide us with additional information for tax purposes. Depending on Users’ location, they may have to fill out a form with some combination of first and last name, residential address, social security number or employer identification number, country of citizenship, foreign tax identification number, date of birth, nonprofit registration number (for nonprofit businesses), bank account Information, phone number.  
  
All payment data such as credit/debit card and bank information is stored on a PCI-compliant payment gateway services data storage. They maintain this data on secure servers behind a firewall in an encrypted format.  
  
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands including Visa, MasterCard, AMEX.

* * *

### Sign-up data

 To simplify the sign-up process, Users may also be using their Facebook or Google account. We will ask permission to access basic information from this User’s Facebook or Google account, such as name, email, and profile picture. Users can choose to stop sharing this information with us at any time by going to Facebook or Google to remove SubscribeStar’s access to that account and your ability to log in. 

* * *

### Additional data

You, as a Star, also can choose to add more information to your profile, such as a geographical location, social media links, and anything else under the profile’s description. This information will be viewable and accessible to all of your profile page visitors.   
  
We will store and analyze all such information along with any comments or messages you submit to this Platform while the account is active.

* * *

### Security of your information

The security, integrity, and confidentiality of User’s Personal Information are extremely important to us.  
  
We implemented technical and administrative security measures that are designed to protect Personal Information from unauthorized access, misuse, unlawful disclosure, destruction, and unwanted modification while following the industry's best practices.  
  
If you provide us with your Financial Information, this data is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with AES-256 encryption. We do not possess, store or use the full set of your Financial Information within our Service.  
  
Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards. We also undergo a strict PCI compliance inspection regularly to ensure your information is well protected.

* * *

### Responsibility

All Users of this Website shall be solely responsible for their computer virus protection. The Users won't hold us liable for any damages or losses in cases that involve malware, ransomware, or other malicious code introduced to their system without any connection to our Service or by any third party.  
  
All Users of this Website agree do not hold liable this Service, our directors, officers, employees, affiliates, agents, contractors, interns, suppliers, service providers, or licensors for any injury, loss, claim, or any direct, indirect, incidental, punitive, special, or consequential damages of any kind, including, but not limited to lost profits, lost revenue, lost savings, loss of data, replacement costs, or any similar damages, whether based in contract, tort (including negligence), strict liability or otherwise, arising from the malicious actions or inactions directed by any third party toward the User of this Website. These malicious events may include, but are not limited to security breaches occurring on the corresponding accounts of social networks, security leaks originating by and from the third parties, as well as an unauthorized use of the login/sign-up credentials that happened due to the Users’ negligence, or other similar reasons.

* * *

### Cookies Policy

SubscribeStar is committed to respecting your privacy and ensuring transparency regarding the way we use cookies on our website. This Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how we use them, and your options for managing them. By using the SubscribeStar website, you consent to our use of cookies as outlined in this policy.

#### What Are Cookies?

Cookies are small text files placed on your device when you visit a website. These files help us enhance your experience by remembering your preferences, improving site performance, and providing personalized content. Cookies can be either _session cookies_ (deleted after you close your browser) or _persistent cookies_ (remain on your device until deleted or expire).

#### How We Use Cookies

SubscribeStar uses cookies to:

* Provide essential services and functions on our website.
* Improve your experience by remembering your preferences and settings.
* Analyze site performance and understand how users interact with the site.

> We don’t use cookies for targeted advertising, nor do we sell any information collected through cookies to third-party marketing services.

#### Types of Cookies We Use

We use the following types of cookies:

* **Strictly Necessary Cookies:** These are essential for you to browse the platform and use its features. These cookies cannot be opted out of, as they are required for the basic functionality of the website.
* **Functional Cookies:** These cookies allow us to remember your choices and preferences, such as language, region settings, or accessing your account. Functional cookies are also essential for a fully customized experience and cannot be opted out of without potentially affecting the site's functionality.
* **Performance Cookies:** These cookies collect information about how visitors use our site, helping us improve performance and functionality. This includes Google Analytics cookies, which gather aggregated data on user interactions (e.g., pages visited, time spent on pages, bounce rate) to help us understand user behavior and enhance site performance. All information collected by Google Analytics cookies is anonymous and used solely for analytical purposes.

> Please note that if, as a Star, you opt out of Google Analytics cookies, it may impact your ability to conduct your Google Analytics integration effectively, potentially affecting your ability to track key metrics and monitor the success of your marketing strategies.

* **Third-Party Cookies:** We may allow third parties to set cookies on your device through our website. These third parties may include services like ShareThis, and others. We do not control these third-party cookies; for more information, please refer to the respective privacy and cookie policies of these third parties.

#### Managing Your Cookie Preferences

You have the right to manage your cookie preferences. When you first visit SubscribeStar, you will see a banner allowing you to accept or decline cookies. You can adjust these settings or disable certain cookies at any time by:

* **Using the Cookie Consent Tool on SubscribeStar:** We provide a [cookie consent management tool](https://www.subscribestar.com/account/cookies_privacy_settings) that allows you to review and adjust your cookie settings by category (e.g., Strictly Necessary, Performance, Functional, and Third-Party cookies). You can opt in or out of specific categories, except for Strictly Necessary and Functional cookies, which are essential for our website’s functionality. 
* **Opting Out of Google Analytics:** To prevent Google Analytics from collecting your information, you can install the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) or simply opt out using our [cookie consent management tool](https://www.subscribestar.com/account/cookies_privacy_settings).
* **Using Your Browser Settings:** Most web browsers allow you to manage your cookie settings directly through their settings. You can block or delete cookies as desired. Instructions for managing cookies on popular browsers can be found below:
    * **Google Chrome:** [Manage cookies in Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647)
    * **Mozilla Firefox:** [Manage cookies in Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)
    * **Safari:** [Manage cookies in Safari](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac)
    * **Microsoft Edge:** [Manage cookies in Edge](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/4027947/windows-delete-cookies)

> Disabling cookies via browser setting may and will impact the functionality of SubscribeStar and will affect your ability to access all features.

* **Opting Out of All Cookies:** If you wish to opt out of all cookies, including Strictly Necessary Cookies (i.e., Essential Cookies), you must leave SubscribeStar and refrain from using it in any way. Strictly Necessary Cookies are essential for the site’s functionality, and disabling them may prevent the site from operating correctly.

#### Updates to this Policy

We may update our Cookies Policy from time to time to reflect changes in technology, legal requirements, or our business practices. It is your responsibility to monitor changes to this policy to stay compliant and use the platform to its full capacity.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions or concerns about our use of cookies, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.subscribestar.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* * *

### Use of collected information

Collected Personal Information helps us learn about your browser and operating system to improve the quality of your experience with the Service.  
  
We may use the Personal Information we collect for one or more of the following purposes:

* To fulfill or meet the reason you provided the information. For example, if you share your name and contact information to ask a question about this Platform, or communicate with us through E-mail, our Website, our social media pages, or by telephone, we will use that Personal Information to respond to your inquiry and communicate with you. If you provide your Personal Information to make a purchase (i.e., subscription), we will use that information to process your payment. We may also save your information to facilitate recurring purchases by you or process your other requests.
* To have a means of communicating with you about transactions with us (i.e., subscriptions, refunds, or payouts) and send you information or request feedback about your transactions, our services, and features on our Website, or changes to our policies.
* To provide, support, personalize, and develop our Website, social media pages, products, and services.
* To create, manage, maintain, customize, and secure your account with us.
* To process your requests, transactions, and payments and prevent transactional fraud and otherwise abuse of the Platform and its Users.
* To provide you with support and to respond to your inquiries, including to investigate and address your concerns and monitor and improve our responses.
* To personalize your Website experience and to deliver content and service offerings relevant to your interests, including targeted offers through our Website, and via E-mail (with your consent, where required by law).
* To help maintain the safety, security, and integrity of our Website, products, services, databases, other technology assets, and business as a whole.
* For testing, research, analysis, and product development, including to develop and improve our Website, products, and services. 

* * *

### Disclosure of the collected information

We may disclose the Personal Information we collect to respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations. 

* * *

### Sharing information internally

#### Sharing Emails

We reserve the right to share E-mail addresses between connected Users on the Platform.   
  
The connection between Users is defined by their relationships on the Platform. Subscription, referral link, payment, dispute, messages, comments make relationships between Users and give them a limited ability to share emails within the platform.   
  
Subscribers agree to share their E-mail addresses with connected Stars and Referral Associates. Referral Associate agrees to share their E-mail addresses with Stars, while Stars agree to share their E-mail addresses with Referral Associates.   
  
All users agree to share their E-mail addresses with us.

#### Sharing physical addresses

Star can access Subscriber's personal postal address (i.e., shipping address) information only if this Subscriber agreed to share their personal address with all or any Stars they are subscribed to.   
  
The address information can only be used in order to deliver tangible products and cannot be shared by the Star with anyone else, even if the User gave a personal agreement on this.

#### Sharing names and aliases

Star and Referral Associate are unable to see Subscriber's real name unless it is explicitly specified on the Website, or the name is willingly and openly published by the Subscriber.  
  
Subscriber will be identified by Stars and by the Service by the automatically generated Nickname, in case the Subscriber didn't set their Nickname manually.   
  
Users can set and update the Nickname in the Account Settings upon registration or while subscribing to the Star for the first time. Users can change their Nicknames later at any time.

#### Sharing reports

If Service provides reports, logs, or other information to the User, this information can not be shared with anybody in any way unless the Service permits to do so in a written form. 

* * *

### Third-party services

In general, the third-party service providers used by this Service will only collect, use, and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us and will be limited by the Terms of Service of this Website.  
  
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways, banks, and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies with respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.  
  
From time to time, we may request additional information related to the Users' identity, activities, or other facets of the existence of a natural person or a legal entity registered with the Platform. We may have obligations to transfer this information to third-party service providers for verification or other actions necessary for further due diligence related to onboarding, inbound payments, or payout processing.  
  
Although we transmit this information via secure channels and take necessary precautionary measures while doing it, we can't guarantee its safety and integrity after a third-party service gets it in possession.  
  
For these providers, it's mandatory that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your Personal Information will be handled.  
  
Remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider (i.e., subscription, refund, or payout), then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.  
  
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.  
  
Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.  
  
When you click on links on our Platform, they may take you away from our Website, with or without warning. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.

* * *

### Data Retention for the EU Content Creators

As required by the applicable laws of each EU jurisdiction, we retain content creators' data in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).  
  
If any jurisdiction has stricter data sharing and retention requirements, the Platform unconditionally complies with those laws or official directives, regardless of the jurisdiction where the content creator operates.

* * *

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently.   
  
Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on this Website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.  
  
If our Platform is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners.

* * *

### Contact information

 If you would like to correct, amend, or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or want to learn more about this Platform or its services - contact us via [\[email protected\]](https://www.subscribestar.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). 

Log InSign Up[Features](https://www.subscribestar.com/features)[Pricing](https://www.subscribestar.com/pricing)[Developers](https://www.subscribestar.com/api)[About](https://www.subscribestar.com/about)

Privacy Settings

Starcling, LLC, 30 N Gould St, Ste 5085, Sheridan, WY, 82801, US      
  
All copyrights belong to their respective owners. Images and text owned by other copyright holders are used here under the guidelines of the Fair Use provisions of United States Copyright Law.  
  
© 2024 SubscribeStar.com.
